<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="44">
    <author>EDGE Gaming / Castiga</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>BMW X6 M</en>
        <de>BMW X6 M</de>
        <fr>BMW X6 M</fr>
        <es>BMW X6 M</es>
        <ru>BMW X6 M</ru>
        <pl>BMW X6 M</pl>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Bmw X6m is the Worlds first functional low loader that will actually fit your huge machinery.
    It's wider and longer than most others making it ideal for this kind of work.
    You will have loads of costumizations options, and there is more to come!
    Fitted with worklights for nighttime work. Also fitted with detail lights working with every truck.

    The trailer has functioning tensionbelts, these will work on all things made for use with tensionbelt in the original game,
    function with fastening vehicles with these will be added in the future.

    BMW X6 M:
    Price: 72.300€
    Power: 258 - 567
    Torque: Max 750 N⋅m
    Top Speed: 250
    Engine Configurations: x30d - x40d - x50d - M4.4 V8
    Rim Configurations: BMW Original Rims - BMW M Rims - EDGE M Rims
    Wheel Configurations: Communal - Race - Agro
    Size: 3 x 6.5m
    Weight: 2.355kg

    Changelog 1.0.0.0:
    Initial Release]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Fliegl Tieflader EDGE Auflage ist der weltweit erste funktionale Tieflader, der für Ihre riesigen Maschinen geeignet ist.
    Es ist breiter und länger als die meisten anderen, was es ideal für diese Art von Arbeit macht.
    Sie werden viele Optionen für die Kostümierung haben, und es wird noch mehr geben!
    Ausgestattet mit Arbeitsscheinwerfern für die Nachtarbeit. Auch mit Detailleuchten ausgestattet, die für jeden LKW geeignet sind.

    Der Trailer hat funktionierende Spanngurte, die auf allen Dingen funktionieren, die für die Verwendung mit Spanngurten im Originalspiel gemacht wurden.
    Funktion bei der Befestigung von Fahrzeugen mit diesen wird in Zukunft hinzukommen.

    BMW X6 M:
    Preis: 35.000 €
    Größe: 13 x 3 m
    Gewicht: 7.500 kg

    Änderungsprotokoll 1.0.0.0:
    Erstveröffentlichung]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Fliegl surbaissé édition EDGE est le premier chargeur surbaissé fonctionnel au monde qui conviendra réellement à vos énormes machines.
    Il est plus large et plus long que la plupart des autres, ce qui le rend idéal pour ce type de travail.
    Vous aurez une multitude d'options de personnalisation, et d'autres sont à venir!
    Equipé de projecteurs de travail pour le travail de nuit. Également équipé de lumières de détail fonctionnant avec tous les camions.

    La bande-annonce a des courroies de tension qui fonctionnent sur tout ce qui est conçu pour être utilisé avec une courroie de tension dans le jeu original,
    fonctionner avec des véhicules de fixation avec ceux-ci seront ajoutés à l'avenir.

    BMW X6 M:
    Prix: 35.000 €
    Taille: 13 x 3m
    Poids: 7.500kg

    Changer le journal 1.0.0.0:
    Première version]]></fr>
        <es><![CDATA[Fliegl Lowloader EDGE Edition es el primer cargador bajo funcional del mundo que realmente se adaptará a su enorme maquinaria.
    Es más ancho y más largo que la mayoría de los demás, lo que lo hace ideal para este tipo de trabajo.
    Tendrás un montón de opciones de disfraces, ¡y hay más por venir!
    Equipados con faros de trabajo para trabajo nocturno. También equipado con luces de detalle trabajando con todos los camiones.

    El tráiler tiene cinturones de tensión en funcionamiento, estos funcionarán en todas las cosas hechas para usar con el cinturón de tensión en el juego original.
    La función con los vehículos de sujeción con estos se añadirá en el futuro.

    BMW X6 M:
    Precio: 35.000 €
    Tamaño: 13 x 3m
    Peso: 7.500kg

    Registro de cambios 1.0.0.0:
    Versión inicial]]></es>
        <ru><![CDATA[Fliegl Lowloader EDGE edition - первый в мире функциональный низкорамный погрузчик, который действительно подойдет для вашей огромной техники.
    Он шире и длиннее, чем большинство других, что делает его идеальным для такой работы.
    У вас будет множество вариантов расчета стоимости, и это еще не все!
    Оснащен фарами для работы в ночное время. Также оснащен детальными огнями, работающими с каждым грузовиком.

    В трейлере есть работающие натяжные ремни, они будут работать на всех вещах, сделанных для использования с натяжными ремнями в оригинальной игре,
    функция с креплением автомобилей с этим будет добавлена в будущем.

    BMW X6 M:
    Цена: 35.000 €
    Размер: 13 х 3 м
    Вес: 7.500 кг

    Журнал изменений 1.0.0.0:
    Первый выпуск]]></ru>
        <pl><![CDATA[Edycja Fliegl Lowloader EDGE to pierwsza na świecie funkcjonalna ładowarka niskopodwoziowa, która rzeczywiście pasuje do ogromnych maszyn.
    Jest szerszy i dłuższy niż większość innych, co czyni go idealnym do tego rodzaju pracy.
    Będziesz mieć mnóstwo opcji kostiumów, a jest ich więcej!
    Wyposażone w reflektory robocze do pracy w nocy. Wyposażony również w oświetlenie szczegółowe współpracujące z każdą ciężarówką.

    Przyczepa ma działające paski napinające, które będą działać na wszystkie rzeczy wykonane z użyciem paska napinającego w oryginalnej grze,
    funkcja z pojazdami mocującymi z tymi zostanie dodana w przyszłości.

    BMW X6 M:
    Cena: 35 000 €
    Rozmiar: 13 x 3 m
    Waga: 7.500 kg

    Dziennik zmian 1.0.0.0:
    Pierwsze wydanie]]></pl>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>BMW_X6M_Icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem rootNode="vehicle" xmlFilename="BMW_X6M.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="EDGE_fliegl" className="Vehicle" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="attacherJoints"/>
            <specialization name="lights"/>
            <specialization name="attachable"/>
            <specialization name="animatedVehicle"/>
            <specialization name="cylindered"/>
            <specialization name="powerConsumer"/>
            <specialization name="foldable"/>
            <specialization name="washable"/>
            <specialization name="wearable"/>
            <specialization name="mountable"/>
        </type>
    </vehicleTypes>
    <l10n>
        <text name="typeDesc_BMW_X6">
            <en>Worlds first functional low loader that will actually fit your huge machinery</en>
            <de>Der weltweit erste funktionale Tieflader, der in Ihre riesigen Maschinen passt</de>
            <fr>Le premier chargeur surbaissé fonctionnel au monde qui conviendra réellement à vos énormes machines</fr>
        </text>
        <text name="name_BMW_X6M">
            <en>Fliegl Lowloader EDGE Edition</en>
            <de>Fliegl Tieflader EDGE Auflage</de>
            <fr>Fliegl surbaissé édition EDGE</fr>
            <es>Fliegl Cargador Bajo EDGE Edición</es>
            <ru>Fliegl Низкорамная платформа EDGE Издание</ru>
            <pl>Fliegl Niskopodwoziowa EDGE Wydanie</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_BMW">
            <en>Communal</en>
            <de>Zwillingsradial</de>
            <fr>Radial double</fr>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_BMW_R">
            <en>Race</en>
            <de>Zwillingsradial</de>
            <fr>Radial double</fr>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_BMW_A">
            <en>Agro</en>
            <de>Zwillingsradial</de>
            <fr>Radial double</fr>
        </text>
        <text name="function_BMW_X6">
            <en>Cargo</en>
            <de>Fracht</de>
            <fr>Fliegl surbaissé édition EDGE</fr>
        </text>
        <text name="DARK GREY" value="0.037 0.037 0.037 1" color="0.037 0.037 0.037 1" material="0"/>
        <text name="ITRUNNER" value="0.037 0.037 0.037 1" color="0.0382 0.0369 0.0482 1" material="8"/>
    </l10n>
    <brands>
        <brand name="EDGE" title="EDGE Industries" image="store/EDGE_Brand_Logo.dds"/>
        <brand name="BMW" title="BMW" image="store/BMW_Brand_Logo.dds"/>
    </brands>
</modDesc>
