<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="47">
    <author>EDGE Gaming</author>
    <translationsby>Castiga</translationsby>
    <version>0.9.0.0</version>
    <iconFilename>GroundPlates_Icon.png</iconFilename>
    <title><!-- en=English de=German jp=Japanese pl=Polish cz=Czech fr=French es=Spanish ru=Russian it=Italian pt=Portuguese hu=Hungary nl=Netherlands cs=Chinese (Simplified) ct=Chinese (Traditional) br=Brazilian-Portuguese tr=Turkish ro=Romanian kr=Korean -->
        <en>Building Blocks</en>
        <de>Bausteine</de>
        <fr>Blocs De Construction</fr>
        <es>Bloques De Construcción</es>
        <ru>Строительные Блоки</ru>
        <pl>Cegiełki</pl>
        <it>Costruzioni</it>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Many different kinds of Decorative Plates/Tiles that can be put on the ground to make your farm look Pristine!
This is the primary pack for something we call Building blocks, it contains many foundations that can be placed down to decorate the ground of your farm.
Cornerstones, walls, ramps & more will be added via separate mods, so you can have a collection that fits your playing style perfectly.

- Its highly advisable to use the in game grid snapping (Default "C" on PC) to make sure they are placed in perfect symmetry.

We are working a lot to make new cool seamless textures for these plates so you can customize your farm just how you like it,
these will be added through rapid updates, as we get them done.

Price:  60 €
Size:   10 x 10 Meters

- Supports the "Seasons" mod.
- We are currently working on making them function as Terrain so they get better wheel tracks, but also hopefully making it so other placeables can be placed on top of them. (without scrips)(console)
- Do you have suggestions to help us figure that out, or just have an amazing texture you want added?
- Please visit our GitHub and contribute from there.
- We also need help with translations, to get it translated correctly to all languages. This can also be done from there.
- We want to make these mods packed to the rim with customization possibilities, so that you can make it fit your farm & fit your gameplay!]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Viele verschiedene Arten von dekorativen Platten / Fliesen, die auf den Boden gelegt werden können, um Ihre Farm makellos aussehen zu lassen!
Dies ist die primäre Packung für etwas, das wir Building Blocks nennen. Sie enthält viele Fundamente, die zur Dekoration des Bodens Ihrer Farm abgelegt werden können.
Ecksteine, Wände, Rampen und mehr werden über separate Mods hinzugefügt, sodass Sie eine Sammlung haben können, die perfekt zu Ihrem Spielstil passt.

- Es ist sehr empfehlenswert, die Rastereinstellung im Spiel (Standard "C" auf dem PC) zu verwenden, um sicherzustellen, dass sie in perfekter Symmetrie platziert sind.

Wir arbeiten intensiv daran, neue, coole, nahtlose Texturen für diese Platten zu erstellen, damit Sie Ihren Betrieb ganz nach Ihren Wünschen gestalten können.
Diese werden durch schnelle Updates hinzugefügt, sobald wir sie fertiggestellt haben.

Preis: 60 €
Größe: 10 x 10 Meter

- Unterstützt den "Seasons" Mod.
- Wir arbeiten derzeit daran, sie als Terrain zu verwenden, damit sie bessere Radspuren erhalten, aber hoffentlich auch so, dass andere Placeables darauf platziert werden können. (ohne scrips) (Konsole)
- Haben Sie Vorschläge, um das herauszufinden, oder haben Sie einfach eine erstaunliche Textur, die Sie hinzufügen möchten?
- Bitte besuchen Sie unseren GitHub und tragen Sie von dort aus bei.
- Wir brauchen auch Hilfe bei der Übersetzung, damit sie in alle Sprachen korrekt übersetzt wird. Dies kann auch von dort aus erfolgen.
- Wir möchten, dass diese Mods mit Anpassungsmöglichkeiten bis an den Rand gepackt sind, damit du sie auf deine Farm und dein Gameplay abstimmen kannst!]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[De nombreux types de plaques / tuiles décoratives qui peuvent être posées sur le sol pour donner à votre ferme un aspect impeccable!
Il s'agit du pack principal pour ce que nous appelons des blocs de construction, il contient de nombreuses fondations qui peuvent être posées pour décorer le sol de votre ferme.
Les pierres angulaires, les murs, les rampes et plus seront ajoutés via des mods séparés, afin que vous puissiez avoir une collection qui correspond parfaitement à votre style de jeu.

- Il est fortement conseillé d'utiliser la capture de grille dans le jeu (par défaut "C" sur PC) pour vous assurer qu'ils sont placés en parfaite symétrie.

Nous travaillons beaucoup pour créer de nouvelles textures sans couture pour ces plaques afin que vous puissiez personnaliser votre ferme comme vous l'aimez,
ceux-ci seront ajoutés par le biais de mises à jour rapides, au fur et à mesure de leur réalisation.

Prix: 60 €
Taille: 10 x 10 mètres

- Prend en charge le mod "Seasons".
- Nous travaillons actuellement à les faire fonctionner en tant que Terrain afin qu'ils obtiennent de meilleures traces de roues, mais aussi, espérons-le, afin que d'autres objets placables puissent être placés dessus. (sans scripts) (console)
- Avez-vous des suggestions pour nous aider à comprendre cela, ou avez-vous simplement une texture incroyable que vous souhaitez ajouter?
- Veuillez visiter notre GitHub et contribuer à partir de là.
- Nous avons également besoin d'aide pour les traductions, pour le faire traduire correctement dans toutes les langues. Cela peut également être fait à partir de là.
- Nous voulons rendre ces mods emballés jusqu'au bord avec des possibilités de personnalisation, afin que vous puissiez l'adapter à votre jeu!]]></fr>
        <es><![CDATA[¡Hay muchos tipos diferentes de placas decorativas / azulejos que se pueden colocar en el suelo para que su granja se vea impecable!
Este es el paquete principal para algo que llamamos bloques de construcción, contiene muchos cimientos que se pueden colocar para decorar el suelo de su granja.
Se agregarán piedras angulares, paredes, rampas y más a través de modificaciones separadas, para que pueda tener una colección que se adapte perfectamente a su estilo de juego.

- Es muy recomendable usar el ajuste de cuadrícula en el juego (predeterminado "C" en la PC) para asegurarse de que se coloquen en una simetría perfecta.

Estamos trabajando mucho para crear nuevas texturas perfectas para estas placas para que pueda personalizar su granja como lo desee,
estos se agregarán mediante actualizaciones rápidas, a medida que los hagamos.

Precio: 60 €
Tamaño: 10 x 10 metros

- Admite el mod "Estaciones".
- Actualmente estamos trabajando para que funcionen como Terrain para que obtengan mejores huellas de las ruedas, pero también esperamos que se puedan colocar encima de ellos otros objetos colocables. (sin scrips) (consola)
- ¿Tiene sugerencias para ayudarnos a resolverlo, o simplemente tiene una textura increíble que desea agregar?
- Visite nuestro GitHub y contribuya desde allí.
- También necesitamos ayuda con las traducciones, para que se traduzca correctamente a todos los idiomas. Esto también se puede hacer desde allí.
- Queremos hacer que estas modificaciones estén llenas hasta el borde con posibilidades de personalización, para que puedas adaptar tu granja a tu juego.]]></es>
        <ru><![CDATA[Много разных видов декоративных плит / плиток, которые можно положить на землю, чтобы ваша ферма выглядела нетронутой!
Это основной пакет для того, что мы называем Строительными блоками, он содержит много фундаментов, которые можно положить вниз, чтобы украсить землю вашей фермы.
Краеугольные камни, стены, пандусы и многое другое будут добавлены через отдельные моды, так что вы можете иметь коллекцию, которая идеально подходит вашему стилю игры.

- Настоятельно рекомендуется использовать привязку игровой сетки (по умолчанию «C» на ПК), чтобы убедиться, что они находятся в идеальной симметрии.

Мы много работаем над созданием новых крутых бесшовных текстур для этих пластин, чтобы вы могли настроить свою ферму так, как вам нравится,
они будут добавлены с помощью быстрых обновлений по мере их выполнения.

Цена: 60 ​​€
Размер: 10 х 10 метров

- Поддерживает мод "Времена года".
- В настоящее время мы работаем над тем, чтобы они работали как Terrain, чтобы они получали лучшие колесные гусеницы, но также надеемся сделать так, чтобы другие размещаемые объекты могли быть размещены поверх них. (без надписей) (консоль)
- Есть ли у вас предложения, чтобы помочь нам понять это, или просто хотите добавить удивительную текстуру?
- Пожалуйста, посетите наш GitHub и внесите свой вклад оттуда.
- Нам также нужна помощь с переводами, чтобы правильно перевести ее на все языки. Это также может быть сделано оттуда.
- Мы хотим, чтобы эти моды были упакованы в обод с возможностями настройки, чтобы вы могли сделать так, чтобы ваша ферма соответствовала вашему игровому процессу!]]></ru>
        <pl><![CDATA[Wiele różnych rodzajów dekoracyjnych płyt / kafelków, które można postawić na ziemi, aby Twoje gospodarstwo wyglądało nieskazitelnie!
Jest to podstawowa paczka dla czegoś, co nazywamy klockami konstrukcyjnymi, zawiera wiele fundamentów, które można położyć, aby udekorować teren swojej farmy.
Kamienie narożne, ściany, rampy i inne zostaną dodane za pomocą osobnych modów, dzięki czemu możesz mieć kolekcję, która idealnie pasuje do Twojego stylu gry.

- Zaleca się stosowanie przyciągania siatki w grze (Domyślne „C” na PC), aby upewnić się, że są one ustawione w idealnej symetrii.

Dużo pracujemy nad stworzeniem nowych fajnych bezszwowych tekstur dla tych płyt, abyś mógł dostosować swoją farmę tak, jak lubisz,
zostaną one dodane za pośrednictwem szybkich aktualizacji, gdy tylko je ukończymy.

Cena: 60 €
Rozmiar: 10 x 10 metrów

- Obsługuje mod „Pory roku”.
- Pracujemy obecnie nad tym, aby działały one jako Teren, aby uzyskać lepsze rozstawy kół, ale także, miejmy nadzieję, aby uczynić je tak, aby można było na nich umieszczać inne obiekty do umieszczania. (bez rysunków) (konsola)
- Czy masz jakieś sugestie, które pomogą nam to rozgryźć, czy po prostu masz niesamowitą teksturę, którą chcesz dodać?
- Odwiedź nasz GitHub i stamtąd wspieraj.
- Potrzebujemy również pomocy w tłumaczeniach, aby poprawnie przetłumaczyć je na wszystkie języki. Można to również zrobić stamtąd.
- Chcemy, aby te mody były spakowane do krawędzi z możliwościami dostosowywania, abyś mógł dopasować swoją farmę do gry!]]></pl>
        <it><![CDATA[Molti diversi tipi di piatti decorativi / piastrelle che possono essere messi a terra per rendere la tua fattoria incontaminata!
Questo è il pacchetto principale per qualcosa che chiamiamo blocchi di costruzione, contiene molte basi che possono essere posizionate per decorare il terreno della tua fattoria.
Pietre miliari, pareti, rampe e altro verranno aggiunti tramite mod separate, in modo da poter avere una collezione che si adatta perfettamente al tuo stile di gioco.

- È altamente consigliabile utilizzare lo snap alla griglia del gioco ("C" predefinito su PC) per assicurarsi che siano posizionati in perfetta simmetria.

Stiamo lavorando molto per creare nuove fantastiche trame senza soluzione di continuità per questi piatti in modo da poter personalizzare la tua fattoria come piace a te,
questi verranno aggiunti tramite aggiornamenti rapidi, man mano che li eseguiamo.

Prezzo: 60 €
Dimensioni: 10 x 10 metri

- Supporta il mod "Stagioni".
- Attualmente stiamo lavorando per farli funzionare come terreno in modo da ottenere migliori carreggiate, ma speriamo anche di renderlo in modo che altri posizionabili possano essere posizionati sopra di essi. (senza script) (console)
- Hai suggerimenti per aiutarci a capirlo, o hai semplicemente una trama straordinaria che vuoi aggiungere?
- Visita il nostro GitHub e contribuisci da lì.
- Abbiamo anche bisogno di aiuto con le traduzioni per tradurlo correttamente in tutte le lingue. Questo può essere fatto anche da lì.
- Vogliamo rendere queste mod piene al bordo con possibilità di personalizzazione, in modo che tu possa rendere la tua fattoria adatta al tuo gameplay!]]></it>
    </description>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateCheckers00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateCheckers01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEDGE00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEDGE01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEDGE02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEDGE03.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEDGE04.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEDGE05.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateAsphalt00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateAsphalt01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateCobblestone00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateCobblestone01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete03.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete04.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete05.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete06.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateConcrete07.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateDefault00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateDefault01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive03.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive04.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive05.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive06.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateEmissive07.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateGlass00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateGlass01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateGlass02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateGridMetal00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateGridMetal01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal03.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal04.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal05.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal06.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal07.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal08.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateMetal09.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateRubber00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateRubber01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateTile00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateTile01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateTile02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateTile03.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateTile04.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateWood00.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateWood01.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateWood02.xml"/>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/PlateWood03.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <brands>
        <brand name="EDGE" title="EDGE Industries" image="store/EDGE_Brand_Logo.dds"/>
    </brands>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="modDesc/modDesc_l10n"/>
    <credits><![CDATA[
## Contributors
- Castiga, EDGE Gaming
## Translations
- Castiga
## Designers
- EDGE Gaming, Castiga]]></credits>
</modDesc>
