<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="47">
    <author>Castiga / EDGE Gaming</author>
    <translationby>Castiga</translationby>
    <version>1.8.0.0</version>
    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <title><!-- en=English de=German jp=Japanese pl=Polish cz=Czech fr=French es=Spanish ru=Russian it=Italian pt=Portuguese hu=Hungary nl=Netherlands cs=Chinese (Simplified) ct=Chinese (Traditional) br=Brazilian-Portuguese tr=Turkish ro=Romanian kr=Korean -->
        <en>Food 'N' Fertilizer Shop</en>
        <de>Futter- Und Düngerhandel</de>
        <fr>Magasin D'Alimentation Et D'Engrais</fr>
        <es>Tienda De Alimentos Y Fertilizantes</es>
        <ru>Магазин Продуктов Питания И Удобрений</ru>
        <pl>Sklep Z Żywnością I Nawozami</pl>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Here you can buy fertilizer of any kind (Manure and slurry excluded), seeds and food for all your animals.
The delivery costs are +10% on current price.
It's fitted with Automatic Lighting.

Price: 25.000€
Size: 21 x 11 Meters

-The Building supports "Seasons" and "Courseplay Six".

Changelog 1.0.0.0:
- Initial Realease.
Changelog 1.5.0.0:
- Added L10N functions and name so it's more understandable for all people, this was previously just in english.
- Updated the mod with more languages.
- Created new Decal textures & added shaders to the building
- Added node for Interactive Zone Markers (Warningstripes can now be turned on and off)
- Created "Seasons" mask support]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Hier kann jede Art von Dünger (Mist und Gülle ausgeschlossen), sowie jede Art von Futter für Ihre Tiere gekauft werden.
Die Zustellung kostet 10% extra.
Die Gebäude verfügen über eine automatische Beleuchtung.

Preis: 25.000€
Größe: 21 x 11 Meter

-Das Gebäude unterstützt "Seasons" und "Courseplay Six".

Änderungsprotokoll 1.0.0.0:
- Erstveröffentlichung.
Änderungsprotokoll 1.5.0.0:
- Es wurden L10N-Funktionen und -Namen hinzugefügt, damit es für alle verständlicher ist. Dies war bisher nur in Englisch.
- Der Mod wurde mit mehr Sprachen aktualisiert.
- Neue Decal-Texturen erstellt und dem Gebäude Shader hinzugefügt.
- Knoten für interaktive Zonenmarkierungen hinzugefügt (Warnstreifen können jetzt ein- und ausgeschaltet werden).
- Maskenunterstützung für "Seasons" erstellt]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Ici, vous pouvez acheter des engrais de toutes sortes (à l'exclusion du fumier et du lisier), des semences et de la nourriture pour tous vos animaux.
La livraison prend 10% sur le dessus.
Les bâtiments ont un éclairage automatique.

Prix: 25.000 €
Taille: 21 x 11 mètres

-Le bâtiment prend en charge "Seasons" et "Courseplay Six".

Changer le journal 1.0.0.0:
- Première version.
Changer le journal 1.5.0.0:
- Ajout des fonctions et du nom de la L10N pour que ce soit plus compréhensible pour tout le monde, c'était avant tout en anglais.
- Mise à jour du mod avec plus de langues.
- Création de nouvelles textures de décalques et ajout de shaders au bâtiment.
- Ajout d’un nœud pour les marqueurs de zone interactifs (les bandes d’avertissement peuvent maintenant être activées et désactivées).
- Création du support de masque "Seasons"]]></fr>
        <es><![CDATA[Aquí puede comprar fertilizantes de cualquier tipo (excepto estiércol y purín), semillas y alimentos para todos sus animales.
La entrega lleva el 10% por encima.
Los edificios tienen iluminación automática.

Precio: 25.000€
Tamaño: 21 x 11 Metros

-El edificio admite "Seasons" y "Courseplay Six".

Registro de cambios 1.0.0.0:
- Versión inicial.
Registro de cambios 1.5.0.0:
- Se agregaron las funciones y el nombre de la L10N, por lo que es más comprensible para todas las personas, esto fue antes en inglés.
- Actualizado el mod con más idiomas.
- Se crearon nuevas texturas de calcomanías y se agregaron sombreadores al edificio.
- Nodo agregado para marcadores de zona interactivos (ahora las franjas de advertencia se pueden activar y desactivar).
- Creado el soporte de máscara "Estaciones"]]></es>
        <ru><![CDATA[Здесь вы можете купить удобрения любого вида (за исключением навоза и навозной жижи), семена и корм для всех ваших животных.
Доставка занимает 10% сверху.
Здания имеют автоматическое освещение.

Цена: 25.000€
Размер: 21 x 11 Mетра

-Здание поддерживает «Времена года» и «Курсовая игра шесть».

Изменения 1.0.0.0:
- Первый выпуск.
Изменения 1.5.0.0:
- Добавлены функции и имя L10N, чтобы оно было более понятным для всех, это было сделано только на английском языке.
- Обновлен мод с большим количеством языков.
- Созданы новые текстуры Decal и добавлены шейдеры в здание.
- Добавлен узел для маркеров интерактивной зоны (теперь можно включать и выключать предупреждающие полосы).
- Создана поддержка маски "Времена года"]]></ru>
        <pl><![CDATA[Tutaj możesz kupić dowolny nawóz (z wyłączeniem obornika i gnojowicy), nasiona i pokarm dla wszystkich swoich zwierząt.
Dostawa zajmuje 10%.
Budynki mają automatyczne oświetlenie.

Cena: 25.000€
Rozmiar: 21 x 11 Metrów

-Budynek obsługuje „Seasons” i „Courseplay Six”.

Lista zmian 1.0.0.0:
- Pierwsze wydanie.
Lista zmian 1.5.0.0:
- Dodano funkcje i nazwę L10N, więc jest to bardziej zrozumiałe dla wszystkich ludzi, było to głównie po angielsku.
- Zaktualizowałem mod z większą liczbą języków.
- Utworzono nowe tekstury naklejek i dodano shadery do budynku.
- Dodano węzeł dla interaktywnych znaczników stref (paski ostrzegawcze można teraz włączać i wyłączać).
- Utworzono obsługę maski „Pory roku”]]></pl>
    </description>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem rootNode="placeable" xmlFilename="data/FoodFertilizerShop.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <brands>
        <brand name="EDGE" title="EDGE Industries" image="store/EDGE_Brand_Logo.dds"/>
    </brands>
    <l10n>
        <!-- multifillingstation -->
        <text name="name_EDGEFNF">
            <en>Food 'n' Fertilizer Shop</en>
            <de>Futter- und Düngerhandel</de>
            <fr>Magasin D'Alimentation Et D'Engrais</fr>
            <es>Tienda De Alimentos Y Fertilizantes</es>
            <ru>Магазин продуктов питания и удобрений</ru>
            <pl>Sklep z żywnością i nawozami</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="EDGEFNF">
            <en>EDGE F'N'F</en>
            <de>EDGE F- Und D</de>
            <fr>EDGE Magasin D'Engrais</fr>
            <es>EDGE F'N'F</es>
            <ru>EDGE F'N'F</ru>
            <pl>EDGE F'N'F</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="EDGEFNFFull">
            <en>EDGE Food 'n' Fertilizer</en>
            <de>EDGE Futter- Und Düngerhandel</de>
            <fr>EDGE Magasin D'Alimentation Et D'Engrais</fr>
            <es>EDGE Tienda De Alimentos Y Fertilizantes</es>
            <ru>EDGE Магазин продуктов питания и удобрений</ru>
            <pl>EDGE Sklep z żywnością i nawozami</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="function_EDGEFNF">
            <en>Here you can buy any type of fertilizer (Manure Excluded), As well as food for your animals. the delivery people take 10%.</en>
            <de>Hier können Sie jede Art von Dünger sowie Futter für Ihre Tiere kaufen. Die Zusteller nehmen 10%.</de>
            <fr>Ici vous pouvez acheter n'importe quel type d'engrais (fumier exclu), ainsi que de la nourriture pour vos animaux les livreurs prennent 10%.</fr>
            <es>Aquí puede comprar fertilizantes de cualquier tipo (excepto estiércol y purín), semillas y alimentos para todos sus animales. La entrega lleva el 10% por encima.</es>
            <ru>Здесь вы можете купить удобрения любого вида (за исключением навоза и навозной жижи), семена и корм для всех ваших животных. Доставка занимает 10% сверху.</ru>
            <pl>Tutaj możesz kupić dowolny nawóz (z wyłączeniem obornika i gnojowicy), nasiona i pokarm dla wszystkich swoich zwierząt. Dostawa zajmuje 10%.</pl>
        </text>
        <text name="function_EDGELights">
            <en>This Building have Automatic Lighting.</en>
            <de>Dieses Gebäude verfügt über eine automatische Beleuchtung.</de>
            <fr>Ce bâtiment a l'éclairage automatique.</fr>
            <es>Este edificio tiene iluminación automática.</es>
            <ru>Это здание имеет автоматическое освещение.</ru>
            <pl>Ten budynek ma automatyczne oświetlenie.</pl>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
